Meet QUBIX - the decentralized GPU marketplace
that's 70% cheaper than AWS
powered by the Qubic blockchain
In the next 6 minutes, I'll show you how
we're revolutionizing GPU compute
with real blockchain transactions,
intelligent matching, and real-time monitoring
First, let's see how easy it is
to become a GPU provider
Watch as I register my RTX 4090
in just one click
Hardware auto-detected in seconds
No complex configuration needed
Real Qubic wallet integration
Ready to accept jobs and start earning
Now let's submit a machine learning job
I'll drag and drop my MNIST training script
Watch QUBIX automatically analyze it
AI-powered job analysis
Automatic requirement detection
Job Type: MNIST Training
Framework: PyTorch
Required VRAM: 8GB
Estimated Duration: 5-8 minutes
Here's where QUBIX shines
Our intelligent matching algorithm
analyzes all available GPUs
and recommends the best options
based on compatibility and cost-benefit
Real-time cost comparison
Intelligent compatibility scoring
72% cheaper than AWS!
Every payment goes through
the real Qubic blockchain
with escrow protection
Watch as we create a secure
escrow transaction
Waiting for blockchain confirmations
Escrow protects both parties
Fully transparent and verifiable
on explorer.qubic.org
Once the job starts, you get a
professional monitoring dashboard
with real-time GPU metrics,
live logs, and progress tracking
Real-time GPU metrics
Live log streaming via WebSocket
Track every detail of your job
Job completed successfully!
Let's switch to the provider view
and see earnings update in real-time
as the job completes
Earnings update every 5 seconds
Automatic payment on completion
Transparent transaction history
Let's recap
The same MNIST training job
costs 18 cents on AWS
but only 5 cents on QUBIX
That's 72% savings with the same performance
powered by real blockchain technology
QUBIX is production-ready,
fully decentralized, and built on Qubic
Try it now at demo.qubix.io